Those who survive the ghost ship are better off dead!
Death Ship is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Alvin Rakoff.
Survivors of a tragic shipping collision are rescued by a
mysterious black ship which appears out of the fog.
Little do they realise that the ship is actually a Nazi torture ship which has sailed the seas
for years, luring unsuspecting sailors aboard and killing them off one by one.
Captain Ashland, played by George Kennedy.
Trevor Marshall, played by Richard Crenna.
Nick, played by Nick Mancuso.
Margaret Marshall, played by Sally Ann Howes.
Sylvia, played by Kate Reid.
Lori, played by Victoria Burgoyne.
Death Ship is a 1980 horror film directed by Alvin Rakoff and starring Richard Crenna, George Kennedy, Nick
Mancuso, Sally Ann Howes, Kate Reid, Victoria Burgoyne, and Saul Rubinek in an early role.
The screenplay by John Robins was based on a story by Jack Hill and David P.
A British-Canadian co-production, the film was shot on-location in Dauphin
Island, Alabama; Quebec City, Quebec; and the Gulf of Mexico.
It was director Rakoff's only horror film, and upon release received
mixed-to-negative reviews, but is considered a cult classic.
The film explores themes of rescue, ship, nazi, ocean, shipwreck.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.